http://www.chicagomusicexchange.com/pages/policies-and-terms

Skip to Content
Appointments preferred » Call to make yours today at (773) 525-7773 or Click for more details!
My shopping cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Menu is closed
Come on the road with us!
Become a CME VIP and get the latest news on gear, giveaways, and deals FIRST!
POLICIES AND TERMSPrivacy PolicyTerms of UseTerms of PurchaseGiveaway TermsExclusions and DiscountsThank you for accessing the chicagomusicexchange.com Website (“Site”) operated by Chicago Music Exchange, LLC. We respect your privacy and want to protect your personal information. To learn more, please read this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Policy.This privacy policy applies to the Site. This privacy policy does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information. Please see below for details.We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by Chicago Music Exchange, LLC. to which the Site links or that links to the Site.INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE1. Information Collection.We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:help make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than oncehelp you quickly find information, products, and serviceshelp us create content that is most relevant to youalert you to new information, products, and services that we offer(a) Registration and Ordering. Before using certain parts of any Site or ordering products, you must complete an online registration form. During registration, you will be prompted to provide to us certain personal information, including but not limited to your name, shipping and billing address(es), phone number, email address, and credit card number. These kinds of personal information are used for billing purposes, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you about your order and the Sites, and for internal marketing purposes. If we encounter a problem when processing your order, your personal information may be used to contact you.(b) Email Addresses.Several locations of the Site permit you to enter your email address for purposes including but not limited to: to register for a contest or sweepstakes; to request us to notify you of new brands, new product styles, or product sizes; to sign up for email newsletters and special offers; or to sign up for the chicagomusicexchange.com. Your participation in a contest or sweepstakes is completely voluntary, so you have a choice whether to participate and disclose information to us. We use this information to notify contest and sweepstakes winners and to award prizes. We may post on the Site the names and cities of contest and sweepstakes winners. By entering a contest or sweepstakes, you may be opting in to receive our email newsletter and special offers and this will be disclosed in the official rules governing the contest or sweepstakes.(c) Cookies and Other Technology. Like many sites, the Site employs cookies and web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or “action tags”) to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.(i) Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. THE SITE’S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER’S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER’S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not “spyware.”(ii) Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on the Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on the Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon.(iii) We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.(iv) As an example, Facebook collects certain information via cookies and web beacons to determine which web pages are visited or what products are purchased. Please note that any information collected by Facebook via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any customer's personal information collected by us.(d) Log Files. As is true of most web sites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access the Site. We may also log your Internet protocol (“IP”) address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)(e) Age. We respect children’s privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. Elsewhere on the Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.(f) Product Reviews. You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location will be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.(g) Bizrate Reviews. Bizrate.com is an independent company that permits shoppers to rate their experiences in visiting and shopping at online stores. After placing an order on the Site, you may receive the opportunity to provide feedback on your experience. This choice is optional and will not affect your order or service from us, whether or not you choose to provide feedback. Your feedback is collected by Bizrate.com, not us, and is governed by their privacy policy, available at http://shop.bizrate.com/content/privacy.html.2. Information Use and Disclosure.(a) Internal Use. We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve the Sites’ content and layout, to improve outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to the Site. In order to facilitate such use and the other use described in this Section 2, we may share your information with affiliates under Chicago Music Exchange's control.(b) Communications with You: We will use your personal information to communicate with you about the Site and your orders and deliveries. Also, we may send you a confirmation email when you register with us. We may send you a service-related announcement on the rare occasions when it is necessary (for example, if we must temporarily suspend our service for maintenance.) Also, you may submit your email address for reasons such as to register for a contest or sweepstakes; to request us to notify you of new brands, new product styles, or product sizes; to sign up for email newsletters and special offers; or to sign up for the Chicagomusicexchange.com news. If you submit your email address, we use it to deliver the information to you. We always permit you to unsubscribe or opt out of future emails (see the opt out section, below, for more details). Because we have to communicate with you about orders that you choose to place, you cannot opt out of receiving emails related to your orders.(c) External Use. We want to provide you with excellent service and to offer you a great selection. We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone other than to affiliates under Chicago Music Exchange's control, except that:(i) As do most catalog and Internet retailers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. For example, in order to deliver products to you, we must share some information. We partner with third parties (such as the U.S. Postal Service, United Parcel Service, and Federal Express) to ship products, to ensure delivery, and so that we can obtain feedback, improve the quality of our service, and measure and improve the quality of the service of the third party. In the example of shippers, we provide them some personally identifiable information such as your name, shipping address, email, and phone number.(ii) Similarly, to help you buy products and provide customer service to you, we must provide your credit card number to financial-services corporations such as credit-card processors and issuers. When we submit your credit card number for authorization, we use state-of-the-art data encryption to protect your information. (More on this below in Data Security.)(iii) We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use the Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.(iv) We will not sell (or trade or rent) personally identifiable information to other companies as part of our regular course of business. However, it’s possible that we might acquire or merge with or be acquired by another company or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect.(v) We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any user.(vi) We may publicly disclose the name, city, and state of the contest and sweepstakes winners.DATA SECURITYThe Site incorporates physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, including Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) for all financial transactions through the Site. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. Finally, we rely on third-party service providers for the physical security of some of our computer hardware. We believe that their security procedures are adequate. For example, when you visit the Site, you access servers that are kept in a secure physical environment, behind a locked cage and an electronic firewall.While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline.OPT OUT/CORRECTIONSUpon your request, we will(a) correct or update your personal information;(b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or(c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account.You can make these requests by calling 773-525-7773 or emailing your request to info@chicagomusicexchange.com Please do not email your credit-card number or other sensitive information.OFFLINE COLLECTION, USE & DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATIONAs you might expect from us, the majority of information that we collect is obtained through the Site, and this Privacy Policy applies only to that online collection of personal information. We also may collect information offline, where we also try to protect the privacy of your personal information. One example involves someone calling us to place an order or to ask questions. When someone calls, we will ask only for the personal information we need in order to place the order or to answer the question. When we need to store information (such as order information), we will enter it into our database through SSL encryption. (See the Data Security section above for more information). Another example involves faxes. If you fax something to us, we will act upon the fax and then either store it a locked repository or we will shred the fax if there is no need to retain the information. There are other ways we could learn of personal information offline (for example, we suppose someone could send us a letter including some return address information), and this Policy doesn’t discuss or try to predict all of those methods or uses. As we mentioned, we will try to treat offline collection, uses, and disclosures consistently with our relevant online practices.UPDATES TO THIS POLICYIf we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on the Site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so you will know if the Privacy Policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us at 1-888-686-7872 or help@chicagomusicexchange.com.TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USEThe Chicago Music Exchange Web site at www.chicagomusicexchange.com (the "Site") is a copyrighted work belonging to Chicago Music Exchange, Inc. ("Chicago Music Exchange "). Chicago Music Exchange grants you the right to use the Site subject to the terms and conditions of use ("Terms of Use") set forth below. PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, OTHER THAN TO READ THESE TERMS OF USE FOR THE FIRST TIME, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR USE THIS SITE.LICENSESubject to these Terms of Use, Chicago Music Exchange grants you a limited, royalty-free license to view the materials contained on the Site (the "Materials") and make such copies only as may be incidentally created during your exercise of the foregoing through the normal operation of a commercially available web browser and a gateway cache and proxy obtaining the Materials from the Chicago Music Exchange server. You are not granted any right to use Chicago Music Exchange trademarks, logos, trade dress (including without limitation the layout of the Site) or other marks, and all such items shall remain the exclusive property of Chicago Music Exchange.MODIFICATIONChicago Music Exchange reserves the right at any time and from time to time to modify or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the Site or any part thereof with or without notice. You agree that Chicago Music Exchange will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension, or discontinuance of the Site.SECURED AREASYour use of any areas of the Site secured by a user name/login screen ("Secured Areas"), including but not limited to purchases of products from the Site, is governed by the terms and conditions of a separate agreement. You are granted no rights or licenses to use the Secured Areas under this Agreement.MAILINGSBy submitting your name, e-mail address, and any other personal information to Chicago Music Exchange, you hereby grant Chicago Music Exchange, subject to the Chicago Music Exchange Privacy Policy a royalty-free license to use and disclose this information, including but not limited to using and disclosing such information in connection with periodic mailings to you about Chicago Music Exchange products, services, and news ("Mailings"). The terms and conditions of this Agreement shall apply to all such Mailings.SUBMISSIONSAll remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, data, personal information, resumes, questions or other information communicated to Chicago Music Exchange through the Site, by facsimile or through the mail (electronic or otherwise) (a "Submission") will forever be the property of Chicago Music Exchange. Chicago Music Exchange will not treat any Submission as confidential or proprietary and will not be liable for the use of any ideas for its business (including, without limitation, service or promotion ideas) and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in future Chicago Music Exchange services or operations. Without limitation, Chicago Music Exchange will have exclusive ownership of all present and future existing rights to the Submission for any commercial or other purpose whatsoever, without compensation to you or any other person sending the Submission. You acknowledge that you are responsible for whatever material you submit, and you, not Chicago Music Exchange, have full responsibility for the Submission, including its legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality, and copyright.SITE USE RULESOur Site may only be used for lawful purposes. Chicago Music Exchange specifically prohibits any use of our Site, and all users agree not to use our Site, for any of the following: Posting any incomplete, false or inaccurate information or information which is not your own accurate information;Posting of any material that defames, harasses, threatens, embarrasses, or abuses others; is racially or ethically offensive; or is obscene, abusive, hateful, pornographic, vulgar, or harmful to anyone, but especially to children;Deleting or revising any material posted by any other person or entity;If you have a password allowing access to a non-public area of our Site, disclosing to or sharing your password with any third parties or using your password for any unauthorized purpose;Harming minors in any way;Impersonating any person or entity or falsely stating or otherwise misrepresenting your affiliation with a person or entity; or Aggregating, copying or duplicating in any manner any of the materials or information available from our Site.We do not knowingly collect identifiable information from anyone under thirteen years of age.REGISTRATION AND PASSWORDSIf you register on our Site, you agree to provide accurate and complete information about yourself and to maintain and update such information so it remains accurate and complete following registration. Failure to provide accurate and complete information or to update such information shall be adequate grounds for us to either suspend or terminate your account. Upon completing the registration process, you will receive a password and user name. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and user name and are responsible for any activities that occur under your password and user name.ACCURACY OF CONTENT AND PRICING INFORMATIONBecause prices, product descriptions and availability can change quickly, Chicago Music Exchange does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information provided on the Site. Also, Chicago Music Exchange may make changes to the information contained herein, including to the products and prices described in the site, at any time, without prior notice to you (including after you have submitted your order). Information at this Site is periodically updated, but it may not be current or complete at the moment you visit this Site and may contain errors or inaccuracies. In no event shall Chicago Music Exchange or its service or product providers be liable to you in any manner whatsoever for any decision made by you, or for any act or failure to act by you, in reliance upon information provided at this Site. If a product you purchase does not match the description on the Site, as your sole and exclusive remedy you may return the product, unused, to Chicago Music Exchange and receive a refund of your purchase price.Items in your shopping cart will reflect the most recent price displayed on the item's product detail page. Prices are frequently updated to adjust for different sales, limited pricing, and other discounting. Therefore, prices on the product detail page and in your cart may change after such updates to reflect the current prices. Placing items in your cart does not reserve the current prices shown at that time, and prices are reserved only by placing an order. From time to time, despite our efforts, a small number of the items in our catalog may be mispriced. Please note that such errors or inaccuracies may be related to product descriptions, pricing and availability. In the event of a pricing error, Chicago Music Exchange will take one of the following options: (1) If an item's correct price is lower than our stated price, we will charge the lower amount and ship you the item; or (2) if an item's correct price is higher than our stated price, we will, at our discretion, either contact you for instructions before shipping or cancel your order and notify you of such cancellation. We apologize for any inconvenience. If you are not satisfied with your purchase due to any errors or inaccuracies, you may return it in accordance with our return procedure. Discounts are limited-time offers and are not valid with other offers.LIMITED QUANTITIESAll products, including those identified as Closeouts and Limited Quantity items are limited to stock on hand and are offered on a first come, first served basis.LIST PRICESList Price is the suggested retail selling price of a product provided to us by manufacturers. We may commonly sell products at prices lower than List Price, and, for any given product, no sales may have occurred at List Price.List Price is a benchmark to compare our discounts from List Price to pricing offered by other retailers. Whether other retailers sell at List Price will vary by product, geographic location, type of store, and over time.Although we periodically update the List Prices in our direct mail offerings and on our website as we receive them, in some cases manufacturers may change a suggested retail price without notice to us.Please contact the manufacturer of a specific product for the most up-to-date List Price information.List Prices quoted for house or private label brands are developed internally in consideration of comparable name brand products. We may commonly sell such products at prices lower than List Price and, for any given product, no sales may have occurred at List Price.Although our limited time events are intended to be limited time events, our low prices offered during these events may continue in effect after the event.Values associated with items labeled "free with purchase" are based upon list price.DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIESTHE INFORMATION ON THE SITE IS PROVIDED "AS IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, REGARDING THE INFORMATION ON THIS SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL WARRANTIES OF TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, in which case any implied warranties shall be limited to the minimum scope and period permitted by law.LIMITATION OF LIABILITYIN NO EVENT SHALL CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES, ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE INFORMATION ON OUR SITE. CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE'S TOTAL CUMULATIVE LIABILITY IN CONNECTION WITH THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND THE USE OF THE SITE, WHETHER IN CONTRACT OR TORT OR OTHERWISE, SHALL NOT EXCEED $1,000. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.COPYRIGHTThe Site and the Materials are copyrighted works of Chicago Music Exchange and/or its suppliers. Neither the Site nor the Materials may be reproduced, displayed, modified or adapted, distributed or transmitted in any form by any means (including, but not limited to, electronic duplication or transmission) without the prior written permission of Chicago Music Exchange.AMENDMENTChicago Music Exchange may at any time revise these Terms of Use by updating this posting. By using this Site, you agree to be bound by any such revisions, and you should periodically visit this page of the Site to examine the then-current Terms of Use by which you are bound. Certain provisions of these Terms of Use may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages of this Site.NOTICEIf you have any questions about these Terms of Use or our Privacy Policy, you may contact Chicago Music Exchange at:Chicago Music Exchange Inc.3316 N Lincoln AveChicago, IL 60657773-525-7773GENERALIf any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable for any reason, the remaining provisions hereof shall be unaffected and remain in full force and effect. These Terms of Use shall for all purposes be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois as those laws are applied to contracts entered into and to be performed entirely in Illinois, without regard to conflicts of law provisions. Any suit or proceeding arising out of or relating to these Terms of Use shall be commenced exclusively in state or federal court in Cook County, Illinois, and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts.ENTIRE AGREEMENTOther than as specifically provided in any separate formal purchase agreement between you and Chicago Music Exchange, these terms and conditions (this "Agreement") apply to all of your online purchases from the website at www.chicagomusicexchange.com (the "Site") and may NOT be altered, supplemented, or amended by you through the use of any other document(s). Any attempt to alter, supplement, or amend this document or to enter an order for product(s) which is subject to additional or altered terms and conditions will be null and void, unless otherwise agreed to in a written agreement signed by both you and Chicago Music Exchange.ACCEPTANCEBy purchasing products and/or services from the Site, you agree to be bound by and accept this Agreement. Orders are not binding upon Chicago Music Exchange until accepted by Chicago Music Exchange. We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone. Chicago Music Exchange will indicate its acceptance of an order by acknowledging your order by reply email or by shipping the ordered items to you.PRICINGBecause prices, product descriptions, and availability can change quickly, Chicago Music Exchange does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of the information provided on the Site. Many of the items online are also available for sale at our physical retail store. Please contact us about the condition and availability of specific products. For more on our pricing policies, please refer to our Site Terms of Use.List Price is the suggested retail selling price of a product provided to us by manufacturers. We may commonly sell products at prices lower than List Price and, for any given product, no sales may have occurred at List Price.List Price is a benchmark to compare our discounts from List Price to pricing offered by other retailers. Whether other retailers sell at List Price will vary by product, geographic location, type of store, and over time.Although we periodically update the List Prices in our direct mail offerings and on our website as we receive them, in some cases manufacturers may change a suggested retail price without notice to us.Please contact the manufacturer of a specific product for the most up-to-date List Price information.List Prices quoted for house or private label brands are developed internally in consideration of comparable name brand products. We may commonly sell such products at prices lower than List Price and, for any given product, no sales may have occurred at List Price.Although our limited time events are intended to be limited time events, our low prices offered during these events may continue in effect after the event.Values associated with items labeled "free with purchase" are based upon list price.PAYMENT TERMS - ORDERSInternet orders may be paid for using the following methods: VISA, MasterCard, American Express, Discover, and PayPal, or just call us at 773-525-7773 to place your order. All non-credit-card orders are subject to a 10-business-day hold. We do not accept international credit card payments from international accounts.For international security reasons, please call the store to arrange a Bank Wire: +01-773-525-7773.SHIPPING CHARGES - TAXES AND TITLESeparate charges for shipping and handling will be shown on your order form. As a security precaution, initial orders and orders shipping to alternate addresses may be held for extended verification. We reserve the right to make partial shipments, which will not relieve you of your obligation to pay for the remaining deliveries.All items purchased from Chicago Music Exchange are made pursuant to a shipment contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items passes to you upon our delivery to the carrier. The published rates are for US domestic shipping only. Contact us directly if you wish to place an international order.For more information on our shipping policies, including rates, delivery times, and delays, please call us at: 773-525-7773.If applicable, a separate charge for taxes will be shown on the invoice. We are required to collect sales tax on all orders shipped to Illinois.LIMITED WARRANTYAll new products are sold with the manufacturer's limited warranty. The warranty period and service varies by manufacturer and product. The full text of any such warranty is available, free of charge, upon written request addressed to:Chicago Music Exchange3316 N Lincoln AveChicago, IL 60657CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE PROVIDES NO SEPARATE WARRANTY AND TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS REGARDING ANY PRODUCTS SOLD TO YOU, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, AND INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ALL WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY RIGHTS.If you are not completely satisfied with any product, return it for a full refund of the product purchase price, full credit, or exchange of your choice. We give you 3 days from the shipping date on used & vintage items, and 30 days on new items.Should you find it necessary to return any merchandise, it must be shipped within this 3-day (Vintage/Used items) or 30-day (New items) period. Please follow the return instructions. All returned items must include a Return Authorization Number, be in the original packaging complete with all components including the warranty card and owner's manual and show no signs of wear or abuse; otherwise the return may either be refused or subject to a 15% restocking fee. Credit card returns are issued a credit for purchase price. Refunds are made for product value only, excluding shipping and handling charges.Send your return to:Chicago Music Exchange3316 N Lincoln AveChicago, IL 60657The following items are returnable only if defective OR unopened or unused: strings, harmonicas, microphones, cleaners, polishes, and polishing cloths. Software/soundware, cassettes, CDs, DVDs, and videos may be returned for credit only if they are in their original, sealed packaging. If defective, these items will only be exchanged for the same product.For complete details on our guarantees, shipping, and return policies, please contact our Customer Service Department at 773-525-7773; fax us at 773-525-2775; or write us at Chicago Music Exchange, 3316 N. Lincoln Ave, Chicago, IL 60657.LIMITATION OF LIABILITYCHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE DOES NOT ACCEPT LIABILITY BEYOND THE REMEDIES SET FORTH HEREIN, INCLUDING ANY LIABILITY FOR PRODUCTS NOT BEING AVAILABLE FOR USE OR FOR LOST OR CORRUPTED DATA OR SOFTWARE, OR THE PROVISION OF SERVICES AND SUPPORT. CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR STATUTORY DAMAGES, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOU AGREE THAT FOR ANY LIABILITY RELATED TO THE PURCHASE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES BUNDLED WITH THE PRODUCTS, WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY IN TORT OR OTHERWISE, CHICAGO MUSIC EXCHANGE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY AMOUNT OF DAMAGES ABOVE THE AGGREGATE DOLLAR AMOUNT PAID BY CUSTOMER FOR THE PURCHASE OF PRODUCTS OR SERVICES UNDER THIS AGREEMENT GIVING RISE TO SUCH LIABILITY. Some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.APPLICABLE LAW - RESALE OR EXPORTYou agree to comply with all applicable laws and regulations of the various states and of the United States. You agree and represent that you are buying for your own personal use only, and not for resale or export.GOVERNING LAWThese terms and conditions shall for all purposes be governed by and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the State of Illinois as those laws are applied to contracts entered into and to be performed entirely in Illinois, without regard to conflicts of law provisions. Any suit or proceeding arising out of or relating to this Agreement shall be commenced exclusively in state or federal court in Cook County, Illinois, and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of such courts.HEADINGSThe section headings used herein are for convenience of reference only and do not form a part of these terms and conditions, and no construction or inference shall be derived therefrom.NO PURCHASE IS NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN. A PURCHASE DOES NOT INCREASE THE CHANCES OF WINNING.1. Eligibility: Sweepstakes (the "Sweepstakes") is open only to those who sign up at the online sweepstakes page and who are at least 18 years old at the time of entry. The sweepstakes is open to the legal residents of the United States and is void where prohibited by law. Employees of Chicago Music Exchange (the "Sponsor") their respective affiliates, subsidiaries, advertising and promotion agencies, suppliers and their immediate family members and/or those living in the same household of each are not eligible to participate in the Sweepstakes. The Sweepstakes is subject to all applicable federal, state and local laws and regulations. Void where prohibited.2. Agreement to Rules: By participating, you agree to be fully unconditionally bound by these Rules, and you represent and warrant that you meet the eligibility requirements set forth herein. In addition, you agree to accept the decisions of Chicago Music Exchange, as final and binding as it relates to the content. The Sweepstakes is subject to all applicable federal, state and local laws.3. Sweepstakes Period: Entries will be accepted online September 1 2020 12:00 PM and ending on December 31st 2020 at 11:59PM. All online entries must be received by midnight of that day. All times are (GMT-06:00) Central Time (US & Canada).4. How to Enter: The Sweepstakes must be entered by submitting an entry using the online form provided on this site. The entry must fulfill all sweepstakes requirements, as specified, to be eligible to win a prize. Entries that are not complete or do not adhere to the rules or specifications may be disqualified at the sole discretion of Chicago Music Exchange. You may enter only once and you must fill in the information requested. You may not enter more times than indicated by using multiple e-mail addresses, identities or devices in an attempt to circumvent the rules. If you use fraudulent methods or otherwise attempt to circumvent the rules your submission may be removed from eligibility at the sole discretion of Chicago Music Exchange.5. Prizes: The approximate retail value of all prizes may vary. The prizes change each month. You are not guaranteed to win a prize and your chance of winning is dependent on the total number of eligible entries received. Actual/appraised value may differ at time of prize award. Only one prize per entry. The specifics of the prize shall be solely determined by the Sponsor. No cash or other prize substitution permitted except at Sponsor's discretion. The prize is nontransferable. Any and all prize related expenses, including without limitation any and all federal, state, and local taxes shall be the sole responsibility of the winner. No substitution of prize or transfer/assignment of prize to others or request for the cash equivalent by winners is permitted. Acceptance of prize constitutes permission for Chicago Music Exchange to use winner's name, likeness, and entry for purposes of advertising and trade without further compensation, unless prohibited by law.6. Odds: The odds of winning depend on the number of eligible entries received. 7. Winner selection and notification: Winners of the Sweepstakes will be selected in a random drawing under the supervision of the Sponsor. Winners will be notified via e-mail to the e-mail address they entered the Sweepstakes with within five (5) days following the winner selection. Chicago Music Exchange shall have no liability for a winner's failure to receive notices due to winners' spam, junk e-mail or other security settings or for winners' provision of incorrect or otherwise non-functioning contact information. If the selected winner cannot be contacted, is ineligible, fails to claim the prize within 15 days from the time award notification was sent, or fails to timely return a completed and executed declaration and releases as required, prize may be forfeited and an alternate winner selected. The receipt by winner of the prize offered in this Sweepstakes is conditioned upon compliance with any and all federal and state laws and regulations. ANY VIOLATION OF THESE OFFICIAL RULES BY ANY WINNER (AT SPONSOR'S SOLE DISCRETION) WILL RESULT IN SUCH WINNER'S DISQUALIFICATION AS WINNER OF THE SWEEPSTAKES AND ALL PRIVILEGES AS WINNER WILL BE IMMEDIATELY TERMINATED.8. Rights Granted by you: By entering this content you understand that Chicago Music Exchange, anyone acting on behalf of Chicago Music Exchange, or its respective licensees, successors and assigns will have the right, where permitted by law, without any further notice, review or consent to print, publish, broadcast, distribute, and use, worldwide in any media now known or hereafter in perpetuity and throughout the World, your entry, including, without limitation, the entry and winner's name, portrait, picture, voice, likeness, image or statements about the Sweepstakes, and biographical information as news, publicity or information and for trade, advertising, public relations and promotional purposes without any further compensation.9. Terms: Chicago Music Exchange reserves the right, in its sole discretion to cancel, terminate, modify or suspend the Sweepstakes should (in its sole discretion) a virus, bugs, non-authorized human intervention, fraud or other causes beyond its control corrupt or affect the administration, security, fairness or proper conduct of the Sweepstakes. In such case, Chicago Music Exchange may select the recipients from all eligible entries received prior to and/or after (if appropriate) the action taken by Chicago Music Exchange. Chicago Music Exchange reserves the right at its sole discretion to disqualify any individual who tampers or attempts to tamper with the entry process or the operation of the Sweepstakes or website or violates these Terms & Conditions.Chicago Music Exchange has the right, in its sole discretion, to maintain the integrity of the Sweepstakes, to void votes for any reason, including, but not limited to; multiple entries from the same user from different IP addresses; multiple entries from the same computer in excess of that allowed by sweepstakes rules; or the use of bots, macros or scripts or other technical means for entering.Any attempt by an entrant to deliberately damage any web site or undermine the legitimate operation of the sweepstakes may be a violation of criminal and civil laws and should such an attempt be made, Chicago Music Exchange reserves the right to seek damages from any such person to the fullest extent permitted by law.By entering the Sweepstakes you agree to receive email newsletters periodically from Chicago Music Exchange. You can opt-out of receiving this communication at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link in the newsletter.10. Limitation of Liability: By entering you agree to release and hold harmless Chicago Music Exchange and its subsidiaries, affiliates, advertising and promotion agencies, partners, representatives, agents, successors, assigns, employees, officers and directors from any liability, illness, injury, death, loss, litigation, claim or damage that may occur, directly or indirectly, whether caused by negligence or not, from (i) such entrant's participation in the sweepstakes and/or his/her acceptance, possession, use, or misuse of any prize or any portion thereof, (ii) technical failures of any kind, including but not limited to the malfunctioning of any computer, cable, network, hardware or software; (iii) the unavailability or inaccessibility of any transmissions or telephone or Internet service; (iv) unauthorized human intervention in any part of the entry process or the Promotion; (v) electronic or human error which may occur in the administration of the Promotion or the processing of entries.11. Disputes: THIS SWEEPSTAKES IS GOVERNED BY THE LAWS OF United States AND Illinois, WITHOUT RESPECT TO CONFLICT OF LAW DOCTRINES. As a condition of participating in this Sweepstakes, participant agrees that any and all disputes which cannot be resolved between the parties, and causes of action arising out of or connected with this Sweepstakes, shall be resolved individually, without resort to any form of class action, exclusively before a court located in Illinois having jurisdiction. Further, in any such dispute, under no circumstances will participant be permitted to obtain awards for, and hereby waives all rights to claim punitive, incidental, or consequential damages, including reasonable attorneys' fees, other than participant's actual out-of-pocket expenses (i.e. costs associated with entering this Sweepstakes), and participant further waives all rights to have damages multiplied or increased.12. Privacy Policy:
Information submitted with an entry is subject to the Privacy Policy stated on the Chicago Music Exchange Web Site. Read the Privacy Policy here: http://https://www.chicagomusicexchange.com/pages/terms.13. Winners List: For the names of the winners, please contact us at marketing@chicagomusicexchange.com and in the body of the email type 'Please e-mail me the winners' list for the Chicago Music Exchange Sweepstakes.14. Sponsor:
The Sponsor of the Sweepstakes is Chicago Music Exchange, 3316 North Lincoln Avenue, CHICAGO, Illinois, United States;15. This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Facebook, Twitter, Youtube, Pinterest, LinkedIn or Google. You understand that you are providing your information to the owner of this sweepstakes and not to Facebook, Twitter, Youtube, Pinterest, LinkedIn or Google.Some of our partner manufacturers and vendors have chosen to be excluded from Chicago Music Exchange sales, coupons, and free shipping promotions. For more information about Free Shipping Exclusions, visit our shipping page. For the latest sales, coupons and promotions see our featured promotions page.NOTE: Trade-Ins do not apply toward the purchase of previously discounted items or items on sale unless otherwise specified.Some of our partner manufacturers and vendors have chosen to be excluded from Chicago Music Exchange sales, coupons, and free shipping promotions. For more information about Free Shipping Exclusions, visit our shipping page. For the latest sales, coupons and promotions see our Featured Promotions page.PROMOTIONAL DISCOUNT AND COUPON CODE EXCLUSIONSProducts from the following brands are ineligible for promotional discounts: 3Leaf Audio, 65 Amps, A&F Drum Co., Aguilar, Alembic, Alexander Pedals, Analog Outfitters, Apogee, Arturia, Asher, AVA, b3, Barber, Bare Knuckle Pickups, Bartel, Batson, Behringer, Benson, Bergantino, BilT, Black Cat Pedals, Bogner, Bose, Boss, Breedlove, Bunting, C&C Drum Co., Callaham, Calton Cases, Caroline, Carr, Catalinbread, Charvel, Chase Bliss, Collings, Cordoba, Crescent, Curtis Novak Classic Pickups, D&A Guitar Gear, Daredevil Pedals, Darkglass, Deering, Di Donato, Diego Vila Customs, Diezel, DiMarzio, Dion Guitars, Disaster Area, Disaster Plugs, Divided By 13, Divine Noise, Doc Sweeney Drums, Dr. Z, Duesenberg, Dunable, Earthquaker Devices, EBow, Echopark, Eden, Electro-Harmonix, Elektron, Elixir, Elliott Capos, Elliott Guitars, Elrick, Emerson, Empress, Epiphone, Erlewine, Eventide, EVH, EWS, Fairfield Circuitry, Fano, Fender, Fishman, Fodera, Friedman, Fulltone, Gallien-Krueger, Galloup, Gamechanger Audio, Gator, Gibson, GNG, Greer Amps, Gretsch, Guild, Hammond, Harmony, Heritage, Hiwatt, Horizon Devices, Huss & Dalton, Ibanez, ISP Technologies, Istanbul Agop, iZotope, J.Rockett, Jackson, Jackson Ampworks, Jackson Audio, JAM Pedals, James Trussart, JHS, JJ Guitars, K&K, Kala, Kauer, Keeley, Kemper Amps, Klon, Koll, KRK, LHT Guitar, Line 6, Lollar, Louis Electric, Lovepedal, Lucem, Maegen Wells, Makala, Make Noise, Marchione, MarconiLab, Marshall, Martin, Matsuda, Matthews Effects, Meinl, Meris, Mike Lull, Milkman, Mission Engineering, Moog, Morgan Amplification, Mr. Black Pedals, Mule, Music Man, Music Nomad, Nash, Neat Microphones, NOAH, Novation, Novo, O3 Customs, OD Guitars, Oddfellow Effects, Old Blood Noise, Orange, Origin Effects, Padalka, Paiste, Paoletti, Pearl, Pedaltrain, Phil Jones, Polyend, Prisma Guitars, Protection Racket, PRS, Q Drum Co., Quilter Labs, R.Robinson, Radial, Ramirez, Red Panda, Reverend, Rickenbacker, Rivera, Roland, Roscoe, RYRA, Sandberg, Sankey, Santa Cruz, Scala, Sequential Circuits, Seymour Duncan, Shure, Sire, SKB, Skytop, Source Audio, Spaceman Effects, Squier, Strymon, SubDecay, Suhr, Supro, Swart, Synergy, T-Rex, Tama, Tao, Taylor, TC Electronic, TC Helicon, Tech 21, Teenage Engineering, Tim Bram, Tobias, Tone King, Trick Percussion, Two Rock, Tyrant Tone, Universal Audio, Verellen, Vertex Effects, Victoria, Vilhelm Engstrom, Voodoo Lab, Walrus, Wampler, Waterloo, Waterslide, Whitfill, Wilborn, Wild Customs, Wren and Cuff, Xotic, Zoom, ZVex, .INTERNATIONAL EXCLUSIONSProducts from the following manufacturers are ineligible for international purchase: Aguilar, BeatBuddy, Bigsby, Blackstar, Charvel, Cordoba, D'Angelico, Danelectro, Darkglass, DeArmond, DiMarzio, Dunlop, Earthquaker Devices, Epiphone, Ernie Ball, ESP, EVH, Fender, Fulltone, Gallien-Krueger, Gator, Gibraltar, Gibson, Gretsch, Groove Tubes, Guild, Hagstrom, ISP Technologies, Jackson, Jackson Ampworks, Jackson Audio, KHDK, Korg, Kramer, KRK, Line 6, Lollar, LP, LTD, Ludwig, Moog, Music Man, MXR, PRS, Quilter, Rickenbacker, Sabian, Schecter, Shure, Source Audio, Squier, Sterling by Music Man, Strymon, Takamine, Taylor, Tech 21, Vertex, Voodoo Lab, Vox, Walforf, Walrus Audio, Wampler, Way Huge, Yamaha,GENERAL PROMOTION RULESPromotions are valid on in-stock items purchased at chicagomusicexchange.com. Discounts cannot be combined with any other special offers, closeouts, or negotiated pricing. Promotions are not valid on the purchase of gift cards. Promotions are not valid on past purchases. Pre-orders and other items not currently in stock are not eligible for discount and coupon promotions.For phone orders, please call 888-686-7872.VINTAGE EXCLUSIONSA small percentage of our vintage selection is ineligible for online coupon codes and discounting. If you're interested in one of these guitars, we are more than happy to have a conversation with you! Simply call us at 888-686-7872..
© 2020 Chicago Music Exchange
